Where have you been?
你上哪儿去了?
Right here. Where have you been?
就在这儿. 你上哪儿去了?
Right here. By the entrance to Saks.
就在这儿. Saks的门口.
Where we agreed to meet.
我们约好在这儿碰面的.
We said near the entrance to Saks.
我们讲好在Saks的门口附近.
I was near the entrance to Saks.
我刚才就在Saks的门口附近.
On the other side.
在另一边.
That's not near the entrance.
那不是门口附近.
That's near the escalator.
那是电梯附近.
I was looking for you.
我一直在找你.
Yeah, yeah. You would have walked right by me if I hadn't seen you.
是啊, 是啊. 要不是我看见你, 你早就从我身边走过去了.
Here. Hold this.
来. 拿着这个.
I want to check something.
我想检查一下东西.
What am I, a closet?
我是什么, 柜子吗?
What, you buy everything but the kitchen sink...
什么? 你把你所能想到的东西都买回来了但是没有买水池...
Don't start, Joe.
别说了, Joe.
See? It fits.
看见了? 很合适.
It's very nice with your eyes.
配你的眼睛很漂亮.
Are you satisfied?
你满意吗?
So what did you do?
那么刚才你做什么了?
I went up to the drugstore and... ah,
我去了药店, 还... ah,
had a blood pressure test.
量了一下血压.
Blood pressure?
血压?
You think you have high blood pressure?
你认为你血压高吗?
Well, I've been wondering about it.
Well, 我一直都想搞清楚这个问题.
Besides, the test was free.
再说, 量血压是免费的.
Why do you think you have high blood pressure?
你为什么会认为自己血压高呢?
Marie.
How long have you thought this?
你这么想有多久了?
Why do you never tell me these things?
为什么从不跟我说这些事?
Marie.
You didn't tell me about your bifocals.
你没跟我谈起过你的双光眼镜.
You don't tell me about your blood pressure.
你也不跟我谈你的血压.
If you wore a hat,
如果你戴着帽子,
I wouldn't know you were bald.
我都不会知道你是秃顶.
Let's go. I'm exhausted.
走吧. 我累坏了.
How can you be tired?
你怎么会觉得累呢?
You just took a nap.
你刚刚打了个盹儿.